Hello everyone, in this video, we will introduce you to the Go Z plugin optimization update in the 2020.2 version.
You can click on the help bar in the main menu to download the corresponding plugin.
You will get a folder called Marvelous Designer when you unzip and download the compressed file.
Move this folder to the file path shown in the video.
If you are a user of the Mac system and your Android method is different, please go to the handbook to check the relevant content.
Click on the download button.
Go to the main menu and select Go Z.
Then click on Pass to Marvelous Designer.
A window will pop up, which lists the Marvelous Designer that you have installed in various versions.
Click on the version you are using.
If a safety warning window pops up, please click on Run.
When the installation is complete, run Marvelous Designer.
Now you can see the Go Z menu in the main menu.
Next, let's learn how to get to ZBrush.
Click on the Go Z menu in the main menu.
Then click on the Go Z in the download menu.
Then click on the ZBrush in the download menu.
The settings in the ZBrush window are mainly divided into two pieces.
At the bottom of the object menu, you can select which objects to export.
For example, all virtual models, panels, accessories, or scenes and props.
Or according to the needs, select or cancel the selection of specific objects.
The merge or un-move merge option is used to set whether the merge costume grid peak is along the powder line.
At the bottom, you can select whether to export the costume with thickness.
At the bottom of the basic menu, you can set the unit of export and the ratio of export.
Click on Confirm to complete the export.
Now you can see all kinds of objects imported in the Subtool menu.
And it has automatically assigned a multidirectional group.
Next, let's take a look at the content of the Go Z import settings.
In the input settings window, you can set the type of download, the type of object, the unit of import and the ratio of export.
In the type of download, you can choose to open it to import the file into a new project.
Or choose to increase the file to the existing project file.
In the type of object, you can choose to import the file into virtual models, accessories, costumes, or scenes and props.
You can choose according to the needs.
Finally, you can set the unit of import and the ratio of export according to the needs.
Now let's try to import a character from ZBrush to Marvelous Designer.
We have already set the object type to Avatar.
The character will be imported into Marvelous Designer in the form of a virtual model.
You can continue to use the virtual model related functions.
And wear the costume on it.
Thank you for watching. See you in the next video.